import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'SingleQuestion.dart';

class CquizList extends ChangeNotifier {
  List<SingleQuizQuestion> Clist = [
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the founder of C Programming Language ?",
      option1: "James A Gosling",
      option2: "Dennis Ritchie",
      option3: "Bjarne Stroustrup",
      option4: "Guido van Rossum",
      correct: "Dennis Ritchie",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Which of these is not a valid identifier name ?",
      option1: "a_33",
      option3: "3_aa",
      option2: "_a33",
      option4: "a33_",
      correct: "3_aa",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "C language was invented to develop which operating System.?",
      option1: "Android",
      option3: "Linux",
      option2: "Ubuntu",
      option4: "Unix",
      correct: "Unix",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "How many bytes does 'int = D' use.?",
      option1: "0",
      option3: "1",
      option2: "2 or 4",
      option4: "10",
      correct: "2 or 4",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "In C language, the constant is defined____.?",
      option1: "Before main",
      option3: "After main",
      option2: "Anywhere,but starting on a new line.",
      option4: "None of these",
      correct: "Anywhere,but starting on a new line.",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    /* SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "What does this decleration mean, int x : 4.?",
      option1: "x is a four-digit integer.",
      option3: "x cannot be greater than a four-digit integer. ",
      option2: "x is a four-bit integer.",
      option4: "None of these",
      correct: "x is a four-bit integer.",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question:
          "If ASCII value of 'x' is 120,then what is the value of the H, if H=('x'-'w')/3.?",
      option1: "0",
      option3: "1",
      option2: "2 ",
      option4: "4",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "0",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question:
          "If x is an array of integer,then the value of &x[i] is same as.?",
      option1: "x + sizeof(int) * i",
      option3: "&x[i-1] + sizeof(int)",
      option2: "x + i",
      option4: "None of these",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "&x[i-1] + sizeof(int)",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "What is (void*)0 ?",
      option1: "Representation of NULL pointer",
      option3: "Representation of void pointer",
      option2: "Error",
      option4: "None of these",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "Representation of NULL pointer",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question:
          "In C, if you pass an array as an argument to a function,what actually gets passed.?",
      option1: "Value of elements in array",
      option3: "First element of the array",
      option2: "Base address of the array",
      option4: "Address of the last element of array",
      correct: "Base address of the array",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question:
          "Which of the following function sets first n characters to a given character?",
      option1: "strinit()",
      option3: "strnset()",
      option2: "strset()",
      option4: "strcset()",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "strnset()",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Which is valid expression in C language?",
      option1: "int my_num=100,000;",
      option3: "int my_num=100000;",
      option2: "int my num=1000;",
      option4: "int my num == 10000;",
      correct: "int my_num=100000;",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "What is a lint?",
      option1: "C compiler",
      option2: "Interactive debugger",
      option3: "Analyzing tool",
      option4: "C interpreter",
      correct: "Analyzing tool",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Which is the only function all C programs must contain ?",
      option1: "start()",
      option2: "system()",
      option3: "main()",
      option4: "printf()",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "main()",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question:
          "If integer needs two bytes of storage,then maximum value of an unsigned integer is ?",
      option1: "2^16 - 1",
      option2: "2^15 - 1",
      option3: "2^16",
      option4: "None of these",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "2^16 - 1",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Which of the following is not a reserved keyword for C ?",
      option1: "auto",
      option2: "case",
      option3: "main",
      option4: "default",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "main",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Compiler generates____file.?",
      option1: "Executable code",
      option2: "Object code",
      option3: "Assembly code",
      option4: "None of these",
      correct: "Object code",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Why to use fflush() library function ?",
      option1: "To flush all streams and specified streams",
      option2: "To flush only specified stream",
      option3: "To flush input/output buffer",
      option4: "Invalid library function",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      correct: "To flush all streams and specified streams",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question: "Why is a macro used in place of a function ?",
      option1: "It reduces execution time",
      option2: "It reduces code size",
      option3: "It increases execution time",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      option4: "It increases code size",
      correct: "It reduces code size",
    ),
    SingleQuizQuestion(
      question:
          "Which one of the following is a loop construct that will always be executed once ?",
      option1: "for",
      option2: "while",
      option3: "do-while",
      isFirstAttemp: true,
      option4: "switch",
      correct: "do-while",
    ),*/
  ];
  List<SingleQuizQuestion> get ListOfCquestions {
    return [...Clist];
  }
}
